let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "______ name is John. And my ______ is Johnson.",
        answer: "B. My / surname",
        options: [
            "A. Your / surname ",
            "B. My / surname",
            "C. I / surname ",
            "D. I / name"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Where ______ John from?  ______ from the US.", 
        answer: "A. is / He's ",
        options: [
            "A. is / He's ",
            "B. is / His ",
            "C. am / He's ",
            "D. is / She's"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Pierre is a French boy. ______ from ______ .",
        answer:  "A. He's / France ",
        options: [
            "A. He's / France ",
            "B. His's / French",
            "C. His / France ",
            "D. He / France"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Lisa and Max are Americans. ______ from U.S.A.",
        answer:  "C. They're ",
        options: [
            "A. There",
            "B. Their ",
            "C. They're ",
            "D. Their're"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I live _____ an apartment _____ two American boys.",
        answer: "C. in / with",
        options: [
            "A. in / of ",
            "B. at / with ",
            "C. in / with",
            "D. of/with"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "They are not my _____ books.",
        answer: "A. children's ",
        options: [
            "A. children's ",
            "B. childs ",
            "C. children' ",
            "D. children of"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "“Where _____ now?”  “In her office.”",
        answer: "B. is she ",
        options: [
            "A. is he ",
            "B. is she ",
            "C. is it ",
            "D. is"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "She _____ a uniform.",
        answer:  "D. wears",
        options: [
            "A. wear ",
            "B. to wear ",
            "C. wearing ",
            "D. wears"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Nancy's uncle is a pilot. He _____ all over the world.",
        answer:  "C. travels ",
        options: [
            "A. goes ",
            "B. sees ",
            "C. travels ",
            "D. delivers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "_____ does your father do in his free time?",
        answer: "D. What",
        options: [
            "A. Why  ",
            "B. What kind ",
            "C. How many ",
            "D. What"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "A: _____ does Anthony go to work? B: _____ bus. ", 
        answer: "A. How / By ",
        options: [
            "A. How / By ",
            "B. How well / On",
            "C. What kind / In ",
            "D. How / In"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " _____ _____ languages does she speak?",
        answer: "B. How many ",
        options: [
            "A. How much ",
            "B. How many ",
            "C. Why ",
            "D. Where"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Our teacher gives _____ a lot of homework.",
        answer: "B. us ",
        options: [
            "A. our ",
            "B. us ",
            "C. her ",
            "D. his"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Mike eats cheeseburgers because _____ likes _____ .",
        answer: "C. he / them ",
        options: [
            "A. he / their ",
            "B. him / they",
            "C. he / them ",
            "D. him / them"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "“____ ____ you live with?”  “With my mother and sisters.”",
        answer: "B. Who / do",
        options: [
            "A. What / do ",
            "B. Who / do",
            "C. Where / does ",
            "D. Who / does"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Are there _____ good beaches near the cottage?",
        answer: "A. any ",
        options: [
            "A. any ",
            "B. some ",
            "C. a ",
            "D. the"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "There's _____ open-fire in the living room? ",
        answer: "A. a ",
        options: [
            "A. a ",
            "B. some ",
            "C. an ",
            "D. any"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "_____ she got a dress _____ white?",
        answer: "D. Has / in",
        options: [
            "A. Does / in ",
            "B. Has / on ",
            "C. Have / in",
            "D. Has / in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Maya _____ got a camera. And she _____ have a car either.",
        answer: "B. hasn't / doesn't",
        options: [
            "A. haven't / doesn't ",
            "B. hasn't / doesn't",
            "C. doesn't / hasn't ",
            "D. haven't / don't"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "A : _____ is Jim going to get married?  B : Next month.  A : _____ is he going to marry?  B : His colleague.",
        answer: "C. When / Whom ",
        options: [
            "A. What time / Who ",
            "B. Who / Where",
            "C. When / Whom ",
            "D. Where / *"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "What time _____ Maria usually arrive at school?",
        answer: "A. does ",
        options: [
            "A. does ",
            "B. is ",
            "C. do ",
            "D. did"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "“_____ did you pay ?”  “$ 1000.”",
        answer: "C. How much ",
        options: [
            "A. How many ",
            "B. How",
            "C. How much ",
            "D. Which one"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Can I have _____ tea?",
        answer: "A. a ",
        options: [
            "A. a ",
            "B. the ",
            "C. any ",
            "D. much"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "A: I've got a cold. B: Then you _____ stay in bed.",
        answer: "A. need to ",
        options: [
            "A. need to ",
            "B. better ",
            "C. can ",
            "D. are"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Please _____ make noise.",
        answer: "B. don't ",
        options: [
            "A. didn't ",
            "B. don't ",
            "C. can't ",
            "D. may not"
        ]
    }
];

let elementryf = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "A: _____.    B: No, thank you. I’ve had enough.",
        answer: "D. Would you like some more?",
        optionsd: [
            "A. Would you like a coffee?  ",
            "B. Do you like strawberries?",
            "C. Could you set the table?  ",
            "D. Would you like some more?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "I’ve got toothache. I _____ go to the dentist.", 
        answer:   "B. must  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. have got ",
            "B. must  ",
            "C. couldn’t ",
            "D. couldn’t "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Turn the TV off. No one _____ it!",
        answer:   "C. is watching  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. watches  ",
            "B. watch ",
            "C. is watching  ",
            "D. watched"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Derek’s good at golf but he _____ very often.",
        answer:  "C. doesn’t play  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. aren’t play",
            "B. isn’t playing  ",
            "C. doesn’t play  ",
            "D. didn’t play"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Prague is one of the _____ cities in Europe.",
        answer: "A. most beautiful",
        optionsd: [
            "A. most beautiful",
            "B. more beautiful ",
            "C. beautiful ",
            "D. the most beautiful"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "A city is _____ than the country.",
        answer: "C. more exciting  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. the most exciting  ",
            "B. exciting ",
            "C. more exciting  ",
            "D. excited"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "A: _____ you like _____ biscuit?  B: Yes, please. And I _____ some milk, too.",
        answer: "A. Would / a / ’d like ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. Would / a / ’d like ",
            "B. Do / a / would like ",
            "C. Would / some / ’d love ",
            "D. Would / * / would love"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Would you like _____ tea _____ mineral water?",
        answer:  "C. some / or  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. some / and  ",
            "B. any / or  ",
            "C. some / or  ",
            "D. any / and"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "_____ you _____ a girl _____ fair hair?",
        answer:  "C. Do / know / with  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. Do / knowing / of  ",
            "B. Does / know / of ",
            "C. Do / know / with  ",
            "D. Are / knowing / with"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "_____ dog is running round _____ garden.",
        answer: "C. Whose / our  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. Whose / ours   ",
            "B. Who’s/our",
            "C. Whose / our  ",
            "D. Who’s / ours"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "I’m going _____ Peter tonight.", 
        answer: "C. to see  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. see  ",
            "B. seeing ",
            "C. to see  ",
            "D. saw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Look _____ that picture. Isn’t it beautiful?",
        answer: "B. at  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. on  ",
            "B. at  ",
            "C. in  ",
            "D. in "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "German is _____ English in some ways, but it is more difficult _____  English. ",
        answer: "C. like / than  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. like / then  ",
            "B. as / that  ",
            "C. like / than  ",
            "D. like / like"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "They are _____ readers, they read _____.",
        answer: "C. slow / hardly  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. slowly / hard ",
            "B. slow / hard",
            "C. slow / hardly  ",
            "D. slowly / hardly"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Be _____! Walk _____.",
        answer: "A. careful / quietly ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. careful / quietly ",
            "B. careful / quiet",
            "C. carefully / quietly  ",
            "D. carefully / quiet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "_____ you ever _____ in a car accident?",
        answer: "B. Have / been ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. Has / been ",
            "B. Have / been ",
            "C. Have / be ",
            "D. Have / was"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "I haven’t done it _____ . ",
        answer: "A. yet  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. yet  ",
            "B. already  ",
            "C. just  ",
            "D.  "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "She’s _____ the letter. She _____ it yesterday.",
        answer: "D. written / wrote",
        optionsd: [
            "A. wrote / wrote  ",
            "B. written / written ",
            "C. wrote / written ",
            "D. written / wrote"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Angela _____ Thai food but Frank _____ .",
        answer: "D. has eaten / hasn’t",
        optionsd: [
            "A. have eaten / hasn’t  ",
            "B. has ate / hasn’t",
            "C. have ate / hasn’t  ",
            "D. has eaten / hasn’t"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "She is only 14 years old, but she _____ many tournaments in her life.",
        answer: "B. ‘s already won",
        optionsd: [
            "A. already won  ",
            "B. ‘s already won",
            "C. already win  ",
            "D. ‘ve already won"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "I _____ a very good program on TV last night.",
        answer: "D. saw",
        optionsd: [
            "A. was seeing  ",
            "B. see  ",
            "C. am seeing  ",
            "D. saw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "“_____ did you pay ?”  “$ 1000.”",
        answer: "C. How much ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. How many ",
            "B. How",
            "C. How much ",
            "D. Which one"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "“_____ did the story take place?”  “A long time ago.”",
        answer: "D. When",
        optionsd: [
            "A. How many ",
            "B. What  ",
            "C. Where  ",
            "D. When"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Do you have _____ sisters or brothers?",
        answer: "D. any",
        optionsd: [
            "A. some  ",
            "B. a  ",
            "C. the  ",
            "D. any"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "I want _____ book from the library.",
        answer: "B. a  ",
        optionsd: [
            "A. the  ",
            "B. a  ",
            "C. some  ",
            "D. any"
        ]
    }
];

let preinter = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "A- How _____ languages can your son speak?  B- Three _____.",
        answer: "C. many / languages   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. much / languages  ",
            "B. many / language",
            "C. many / languages   ",
            "D. much / language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "While the waiter _____ up the broken plates, he _____ his finger.", 
        answer: "B. was picking / cut  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. picked / was cutting ",
            "B. was picking / cut  ",
            "C. pick / cut  ",
            "D. picks / cut "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "I _____ round and _____ Paula.",
        answer: "A. turned / saw  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. turned / saw  ",
            "B. was turning/ was seeing ",
            "C. turn / was seeing   ",
            "D. was turning / saw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "He _____ milk in his coffee.",
        answer:  "A. never has ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. never has ",
            "B. has never got  ",
            "C. has never got  ",
            "D. have never"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "We got up late _____ Sunday morning.",
        answer: "C. on  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A.  * ",
            "B. at  ",
            "C. on  ",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "We played tennis _____ two hours.",
        answer:  "D. for",
        optionsp: [
            "A. during   ",
            "B. while  ",
            "C. nothing  ' ",
            "D. for"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "A: I don’t want to talk to _____.    B: And I want to talk to _____ either.",
        answer: "A. anyone / no one  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. anyone / no one  ",
            "B. somebody / everyone ",
            "C. nobody / somebody  ",
            "D. everybody/anybody"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The hotel _____ we stayed was very comfortable.",
        answer:  "C. where   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. which   ",
            "B. that   ",
            "C. where   ",
            "D. when"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Where is the woman _____ ordered the fish.",
        answer:  "A. who ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. who ",
            "B. which ",
            "C. which   ",
            "D. where"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Mike and Jack _____ here five months ago. They _____ in this city for five months.",
        answer: "B. have come / have been",
        optionsp: [
            "A. came / have been    ",
            "B. have come / have been",
            "C. come / were   ",
            "D. has come / has been"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Your clothes smell, and you’ve got a cough. You _____ smoke.", 
        answer: "C. shouldn’t   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. don’t have to   ",
            "B. should ",
            "C. shouldn’t   ",
            "D. have to"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " We’ve known Paul _____ two years. Have you _____ met him?",
        answer: "C. for / ever  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. since / for   ",
            "B. since / ever   ",
            "C. for / ever  ",
            "D. never / ever "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "If you want to learn English, you _____ speak your language in English    lessons.         ",
        answer: "D. shouldn’t",
        optionsp: [
            "A. should   ",
            "B. don’t have to  ",
            "C. must   ",
            "D. shouldn’t"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "I like to relax _____ I’m on holiday.",
        answer: "A. while  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. while  ",
            "B. before ",
            "C. if   ",
            "D. as soon as"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "My bag is so heavy.   “Give it to me. _____ it for you.",
        answer: "C. I’ll carry   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. I’m going to carry ",
            "B. I carry",
            "C. I’ll carry   ",
            "D. I carried"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "I asked him ___ help.",
        answer: "C. for ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. in  ",
            "B. about  ",
            "C. for ",
            "D. by"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Great Britain consists ___ three parts.",
        answer: "A. of   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. of   ",
            "B. with   ",
            "C. from  ",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "He tried, but ___ persuade nobody.",
        answer: "A. could ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. could ",
            "B. couldn’t ",
            "C. can ",
            "D. might "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "-I ___ understand the rule;   ___ I take the examination another time?   -Yes, of course.",
        answer: "C. can’t / may",
        optionsp: [
            "A. could / can",
            "B. may / may ",
            "C. can’t / may",
            "D. mustn’t / must  "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "They are very ______ on music.",
        answer: "A. keen  ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. keen  ",
            "B. fan ",
            "C. like   ",
            "D. respect"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Money from work, usually monthly, is called ______.",
        answer: "B. salary   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. wages ",
            "B. salary   ",
            "C. fee   ",
            "D. pay"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "My sister’s husband is my ______.",
        answer: "B. brother-in-law",
        optionsp: [
            "A. brother  ",
            "B. brother-in-law",
            "C. cousin  ",
            "D. nephew"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "He filled my glass with orange ______.",
        answer: "C. juice   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. coffee  ",
            "B. alcohol   ",
            "C. juice   ",
            "D. water"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "The art exhibition was very _____. I loved it.",
        answer: "C. interesting   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. surprised   ",
            "B. boring   ",
            "C. interesting   ",
            "D. excited"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "My feet are killing me! I find going round art galleries and museums very _____. ",
        answer: "A. tiring   ",
        optionsp: [
            "A. tiring   ",
            "B. worrying   ",
            "C. boring   ",
            "D. frightening"
        ]
    }
];
let preinterfil = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "I worked on a farm _____ the holidays.",
        answer: "C. during    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. for  ",
            "B. since ",
            "C. during    ",
            "D. mon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "She _____ for dinner this evening", 
        answer:   "D. is coming ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. come ",
            "B. came   ",
            "C. comes  ",
            "D. is coming "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "You can tell me your secret. I _____ anyone.",
        answer:   "B. won’t tell",
        optionpf: [
            "A. am not going tell   ",
            "B. won’t tell",
            "C. don’t tell    ",
            "D. didn’t tell"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "I hope _____ some money soon.",
        answer:  "C. to earn   ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. earning  ",
            "B. earn  ",
            "C. to earn   ",
            "D. to earning"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I’d love ____ with you.",
        answer: "C. to go   ",
        optionpf: [
            "A.  to going ",
            "B. go   ",
            "C. to go   ",
            "D. going"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Mike and Jack _____ here five months ago. They _____ in this city for five months.",
        answer:  "A. came / have been    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. came / have been    ",
            "B. have come / have been  ",
            "C. come / were   ' ",
            "D. has come / has been"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "David can go to bed now. He _____ his homework.",
        answer: "B. has finished ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. finish   ",
            "B. has finished ",
            "C. finishes   ",
            "D. finished"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "When I was young, I _____ ice-skating.",
        answer:  "C. used to go    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. went to   ",
            "B. go    ",
            "C. used to go    ",
            "D. going"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The telephone _____ by Bell in 1876.",
        answer:  "C. was invented    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. has invented  ",
            "B. is invented ",
            "C. was invented    ",
            "D. invented"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "English _____ all over the world.",
        answer: "B. is spoken",
        optionpf: [
            "A. speaks ",
            "B. is spoken",
            "C. was spoken    ",
            "D. has been spoken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Don’t wait for me. I _____ late. It depends on the traffic.", 
        answer: "C. might be    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. will be  ",
            "B. am ",
            "C. might be    ",
            "D. am going to be"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Turn _____ the music! It’s too loud!",
        answer: "C. down  ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. on  ",
            "B. round  ",
            "C. down  ",
            "D. after "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Sorry. I _____ one of your glasses.    ",
        answer: "A. have broken    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. have broken    ",
            "B. broke",
            "C. break    ",
            "D. have been breaking"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Could I ______ your pen?",
        answer: "C. borrow    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. give   ",
            "B. lend  ",
            "C. borrow    ",
            "D. make"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "The phone rang _____ I was having supper.",
        answer: "A. while ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. while ",
            "B. while ",
            "C. for  ",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "If I _____ Prime Minister, I _____ increase tax for rich people.",
        answer: "D. were / would",
        optionpf: [
            "A. would be / shall   ",
            "B. will be / will  ",
            "C. am / would  ",
            "D. were / would"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "I’m _____ forward to meeting her very much.",
        answer: "B. looking    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. fallen    ",
            "B. looking    ",
            "C. trying   ",
            "D. giving"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "I live in a house now, but before I _____ in a flat.",
        answer: "B. used to live ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. am using to live ",
            "B. used to live ",
            "C. had used to live  ",
            "D. have used to live "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "When I was a child I_____ drink a lot of milk.",
        answer: "C. used to ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. should ",
            "B. may  ",
            "C. used to ",
            "D. need "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "My friend lives in _____ same street as me.",
        answer: "D. the",
        optionpf: [
            "A. a   ",
            "B. *  ",
            "C. an    ",
            "D. the"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "I work in _____ company that makes _____ carpets.",
        answer: "A. a / *  ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. a / *  ",
            "B. the / the    ",
            "C. the / *    ",
            "D. a / a"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Our flat is small, _____ it’s comfortable.",
        answer: "A. but   ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. but   ",
            "B. so ",
            "C. because   ",
            "D. and"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "I like living here _____ it’s near the shops.",
        answer: "A. because   ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. because   ",
            "B. so    ",
            "C. and    ",
            "D. but"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "“What are you doing tonight?”  “I don’t know. I _____ out, or I _____ at home.”",
        answer: "B. might go / might stay",
        optionpf: [
            "A. will go / am staying    ",
            "B. might go / might stay",
            "C. am going / am staying    ",
            "D. go / stay"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "If I _____ perfect English, I _____ in this class.",
        answer: "C. could speak / wouldn’t be    ",
        optionpf: [
            "A. could spoke / won’t be    ",
            "B. can speak / would be   ",
            "C. could speak / wouldn’t be    ",
            "D. can’t speak / will not be"
        ]
    }
];



let preinterstr = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "I hurt my leg _____ the second half of the match.",
        answer: "D. in",
        optionk: [
            "A. via   ",
            "B. until ",
            "C. for   ",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "_____ my stay in hospital, the nurses looked after me very well.", 
        answer:   "B. During  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. While ",
            "B. During  ",
            "C. For",
            "D. In "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "I _____ get into my house last night because I’d lost my key.",
        answer:   "D. couldn’t",
        optionk: [
            "A. can  ",
            "B. could ",
            "C. managed to   ",
            "D. couldn’t"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "A retired person_____ go to work.",
        answer:   "A. doesn’t have to  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. doesn’t have to  ",
            "B. has to  ",
            "C. have to  ",
            "D. don’t have to"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Hundreds of people _____ for the jobs.",
        answer: "B. have applied  ",
        optionk: [
            "A.  have been applied  ",
            "B. have applied  ",
            "C. have applying   ",
            "D. was applied"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How many times _____ redundant?",
        answer:  "B. have you been made  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. were you    ",
            "B. have you been made  ",
            "C. you ",
            "D. have you made"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "You’re really annoying me. You’re doing it _____ purpose, aren’t you?",
        answer: "B. on  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. in   ",
            "B. on  ",
            "C. out of  ",
            "D. of"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "If you _____ any problems, let me know and I _____ and help you6 straight away",
        answer:  "B. have / will come   ",
        optionk: [
            "A. had / would come   ",
            "B. have / will come   ",
            "C. had had / would come    ",
            "D. have / would go"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "It isn’t ______ job for me to do alone.",
        answer:  "B. an easy enough ",
        optionk: [
            "A. easy enough a  ",
            "B. an easy enough ",
            "C. enough an easy    ",
            "D. an enough easy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "When I counted my change I realized they ______ me $ 3 too much.",
        answer: "B. had given",
        optionk: [
            "A. gave ",
            "B. had given",
            "C. have given    ",
            "D. had been given"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Plans to develop cars on methanol are likely ______ in the future.", 
        answer: "C. to be realized    ",
        optionk: [
            "A. will be realized  ",
            "B. will have been realized ",
            "C. to be realized    ",
            "D. being realized"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Don’t look at your friend’s paper. The teacher warned me ______my friend’s paper.",
        answer: "D. not to look at ",
        optionk: [
            "A. to look at   ",
            "B. I don’t look at   ",
            "C. you don’t look at    ",
            "D. not to look at "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Bill said he didn’t like to study. Bill said, “______”  ",
        answer: "A I don’t like to study  ",
        optionk: [
            "A I don’t like to study  ",
            "B. You don’t like to study ",
            "C. He doesn’t like to study    ",
            "D. We don’t like to study"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "It was the blue car______.",
        answer: "D. which caused the accident",
        optionk: [
            "A. it caused the accident   ",
            "B. caused the accident ",
            "C. it is expensive    ",
            "D. which caused the accident"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "_______ is still uncertain.",
        answer: "D. Who first reported the fire",
        optionk: [
            "A. Why did they lose the match ",
            "B. He is really guilty",
            "C. When will they come   ",
            "D. Who first reported the fire"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "_______ is where you get all your energy from.",
        answer: "C. What amazes me  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. It amazes me   ",
            "B. That amazes me  ",
            "C. What amazes me  ",
            "D. That amazed me"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "“I’d love to come.” she said. She said _______ to come.",
        answer: "C. she’d like   ",
        optionk: [
            "A. she’d liked    ",
            "B. I’d like    ",
            "C. she’d like   ",
            "D. I’d liked"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "I didn’t hear _______ because there was so much noise where I was sitting.",
        answer: "D. what he said ",
        optionk: [
            "A. what was he saying  ",
            "B. what he has said ",
            "C. what did he say  ",
            "D. what he said "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Your information, for _______ I’m grateful, is very helpful.",
        answer: "B. which  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. that ",
            "B. which  ",
            "C. whom ",
            "D. whose "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "I’ll give you my telephone number _______ you want to get in touch  with me again.",
        answer: "B. in case  ",
        optionk: [
            "A. although   ",
            "B. in case  ",
            "C. so that    ",
            "D. as if"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "I’m short ______ money this week. Can you lend me some?",
        answer: "B. of    ",
        optionk: [
            "A. without  ",
            "B. of    ",
            "C. at    ",
            "D. on"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Her ability makes her successful ______ everything she does.",
        answer: "D. at",
        optionk: [
            "A. on   ",
            "B. in ",
            "C. about   ",
            "D. at"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "I’m glad to get rid ______ the responsibility.",
        answer: "B. of    ",
        optionk: [
            "A. from   ",
            "B. of    ",
            "C. with    ",
            "D. without"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "He is occupied ______ the latest report at the moment.",
        answer: "A. with    ",
        optionk: [
            "A. with    ",
            "B. in    ",
            "C. at    ",
            "D. by"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "We suspected him _____ stealing the tape recorder.",
        answer: "C. of    ",
        optionk: [
            "A. at    ",
            "B. with    ",
            "C. of    ",
            "D. on"
        ]
    }
];



let preinterstf = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "_______ you say to her, she still keeps smiling.",
        answer: "C. Whatever    ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. However   ",
            "B. Moreover ",
            "C. Whatever    ",
            "D. Whenever"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "I used to love listening to her, even though _______.", 
        answer:  "D. I could only understand about half of what she said ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. she has nothing interesting to mention",
            "B. we didn’t have a radio to listen to  ",
            "C. she was a good friend of mine ",
            "D. I could only understand about half of what she said "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Susan _____ the mechanic _____ her car yesterday.",
        answer:   "A. had / repair  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. had / repair  ",
            "B. has / to repair ",
            "C. had / to repair   ",
            "D. having / repair"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "She seems _____ better today.",
        answer:  "A. to be feeling  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. to be feeling  ",
            "B. feeling   ",
            "C. feel   ",
            "D. felt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "She went into the kitchen _____ dinner ready.",
        answer: "B. to get   ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. getting ",
            "B. to get   ",
            "C. get   ",
            "D. to have got"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What made you _____ it ?",
        answer:  "A. do    ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. do    ",
            "B. to do   ",
            "C. doing   ' ",
            "D. done"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "I am not used _____ a suit and tie every day.",
        answer: "C. to wearing  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. to wear  ",
            "B. having worn  ",
            "C. to wearing  ",
            "D. to have worn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "I would rather _____ out last night.",
        answer:  "D. not have gone",
        optionfs: [
            "A. not to have gone    ",
            "B. not go   ",
            "C. not to go    ",
            "D. not have gone"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "He admitted _____ the money.",
        answer:  "D. having stolen",
        optionfs: [
            "A. to have stolen  ",
            "B. to steal ",
            "C. having been stolen    ",
            "D. having stolen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "I had my friend _____ me to the airport.",
        answer: "C. drive ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. to drive ",
            "B. driving ",
            "C. drive ",
            "D. driven"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "I should _____ the exam in January, but I was ill.", 
        answer: "C. have taken    ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. be taking  ",
            "B. be taken ",
            "C. have taken    ",
            "D. have been taken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " I had my binoculars_____ when I was at the stadium.",
        answer: "A. stolen  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. stolen  ",
            "B. stole ",
            "C. to steal  ",
            "D. stealing"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "It’s a waste of time _____ his advice. ",
        answer: "A. to ask    ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. to ask    ",
            "B. asking ",
            "C. ask    ",
            "D. having asked"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "He didn’t pass his driving test. He wishes he _____ it.",
        answer: "B. had passed ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. have passed   ",
            "B. had passed ",
            "C. will pass ",
            "D. pass"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "If I _____ taller, I _____ be a policeman, but I’m too short.",
        answer: "C. were / could ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. was / can ",
            "B. had / could",
            "C. were / could ",
            "D. am / will"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "A new prime minister _____ .",
        answer: "B. has been elected  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. has elected   ",
            "B. has been elected  ",
            "C. have elected  ",
            "D. elected"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "I wish that you _______ such a bad headache because I’m sure that you’d have enjoyed the party.",
        answer: "B. hadn’t had ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. didn’t have  ",
            "B. hadn’t had ",
            "C. wouldn’t have  ",
            "D. won’t have"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "I wish we _______ late for this film. I can’t follow the story.",
        answer: "B. hadn’t arrived ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. didn’t arrive  ",
            "B. hadn’t arrived ",
            "C. wouldn’t arrive  ",
            "D. wouldn’t have arrived "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Do you think _______ man will travel to Mars in this century?",
        answer: "B. it is possible that ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. is it possible that ",
            "B. it is possible that ",
            "C. will it be possible ",
            "D. it became possible "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "This application _____ last week.",
        answer: "C. ought to have been sent    ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. should be sent   ",
            "B. must have been ",
            "C. ought to have been sent    ",
            "D. should have sent"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "A: I took Janet to the cinema last night.  A: I took Janet to the cinema last night.",
        answer:  "C. might have taken ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. might take  ",
            "B. may have been taken   ",
            "C. might have taken ",
            "D. must have taken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Why did you take such a risk? You _____ died!",
        answer: "C. comight have  ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. could   ",
            "B. must be ",
            "C. comight have  ",
            "D. may be"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "They always give the available seats to ______ comes first.",
        answer: "A. whoever ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. whoever ",
            "B. whom  ",
            "C. whichever  ",
            "D. whomever"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Nobody ______ objecting to the decision to closedown the factory.",
        answer:  "A. is ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. is ",
            "B. are ",
            "C. isn’t  ",
            "D. wasn’t"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "I have two boys, but ______ of them likes pop music. ",
        answer:  "C. neither ",
        optionfs: [
            "A. either ",
            "B. both  ",
            "C. neither ",
            "D. none"
        ]
    }
];

let preinteru = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Neither of the footballers ______ well.",
        answer: "A. played ",
        optionj: [
            "A. played ",
            "B. play ",
            "C. didn’t play  ",
            "D. do play"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "It was a ______.", 
        answer:   "A. thirty-minute show",
        optionj: [
            "A. thirty-minute show",
            "B. TV show thirty minute ",
            "C. thirty minutes TV show  ",
            "D. TV show of thirty minute"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Her condition improved ______. There was a ______ improvement   in her condition.",
        answer:   "D. steadily / steady",
        optionj: [
            "A. steady / steadiness ",
            "B. steadiness / steady",
            "C. steady / steadily ",
            "D. steadily / steady"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Mr. Hopkins plans on ___ his students ___ the English test tomorrow.",
        answer:  "B. having / take ",
        optionj: [
            "A. to have / take  ",
            "B. having / take ",
            "C. having / to take  ",
            "D. to have / to take"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I simply couldn’t resist _____ you to tell you the good news!",
        answer: "A.  phoning ",
        optionj: [
            "A.  phoning ",
            "B. to phone   ",
            "C. phone   ",
            "D. phoned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "He didn’t even apologize. This made her really angry. _______ he    didn’t even apologize made her really angry.",
        answer:  "C. The fact that   ' ",
        optionj: [
            "A. Why    ",
            "B. What   ",
            "C. The fact that   ' ",
            "D. The reason"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "On entering the restaurant, I immediately realized _____ so popular.",
        answer: "D. why it was",
        optionj: [
            "A. why was it ",
            "B. how is it",
            "C. the fact that was ",
            "D. why it was"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "_______ was have dinner after the meeting.",
        answer:  "C. What I wanted to do  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. What we are to do",
            "B. Which we needed",
            "C. What I wanted to do  ",
            "D. Why he comes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "_______ next was lost in the general uproar.",
        answer:  "A. What the speaker said  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. What the speaker said  ",
            "B. That the speaker said ",
            "C. What did the speaker say    ",
            "D. The speaker said that"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Galileo is supposed _____ the telescope.",
        answer: "C. to have invented ",
        optionj: [
            "A. having invented ",
            "B. have invented",
            "C. to have invented ",
            "D. to invent"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "I won’t waste time _____ to his letter.", 
        answer: "C. replying    ",
        optionj: [
            "A. reply ",
            "B. to reply ",
            "C. replying    ",
            "D. to have replied"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Living in London is expensive. It is expensive _____ in London.",
        answer: "A. to live ",
        optionj: [
            "A. to live ",
            "B. living ",
            "C. to have lived ",
            "D. lived"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "_____, she washed the cup and put it away. ",
        answer: "C. Having drunk the coffee ",
        optionj: [
            "A. Having the coffee ",
            "B. Drinking the coffee",
            "C. Having drunk the coffee ",
            "D. Has drunk the coffee"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "_____ he ran out of the classroom.",
        answer: "A. Turning suddenly, with tears in his eyes ",
        optionj: [
            "A. Turning suddenly, with tears in his eyes ",
            "B. Having tears in his eyes and turned suddenly ",
            "C. With a sudden turn, tearful eyes ",
            "D. With tears in his eyes and a sudden turn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Have you met the secretary _____ last week?",
        answer: "A. hired ",
        optionj: [
            "A. hired ",
            "B. was hired",
            "C. she was hired ",
            "D. when she was hired"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "The hardest thing to do is to start again. The hardest thing you _____ is to start again.",
        answer: "A. have to do ",
        optionj: [
            "A. have to do ",
            "B. having to do",
            "C. should have done ",
            "D. to do"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "His eyes need _____.",
        answer: "D. in",
        optionj: [
            "A. to have been tested ",
            "B. with   ",
            "C. from  ",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Many people think that the Vikings sailed to Canada. The Vikings are thought _____ to Canada.",
        answer: "C. to have sailed  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. to be sailing  ",
            "B. to have been sailed",
            "C. to have sailed  ",
            "D. to sail "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "_____ some money, he didn’t need to work any more.",
        answer: "A. Having made ",
        optionj: [
            "A. Having made ",
            "B. Making",
            "C. To make ",
            "D. Made "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "The examiner made us _____ our identification in order to be admitted to the test.",
        answer: "B. show  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. showing   ",
            "B. show  ",
            "C. to show    ",
            "D. showed"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "The film was so terrifying that I could hardly bear _____ it.",
        answer: "A. watching  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. watching  ",
            "B. to watch ",
            "C. to be watching ",
            "D. to have watched"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "What ___ you ___ at 6 tomorrow?",
        answer: "B. will/be doing ",
        optionj: [
            "A. did/do ",
            "B. will/be doing ",
            "C. do/do ",
            "D. do/did "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "By the end of the first term we ___ many English books.",
        answer: "C. will have read",
        optionj: [
            "A. will be read ",
            "B. read  ",
            "C. will have read",
            "D. have read "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "She ___ in Tashkent five years ago.",
        answer: "B. lived  ",
        optionj: [
            "A. had lived  ",
            "B. lived  ",
            "C. has lived",
            "D. live "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "In the past, Sardor ___ early in the mornings.",
        answer: "D. would wake up ",
        optionj: [
            "A. woke up  ",
            "B. was waking up",
            "C. has woken up ",
            "D. would wake up "
        ]
    }
];


let preintergh = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "They _______________ a new car by the end of the month.",
        answer: "D. will have bought",
        optionqa: [
            "A. will be buying ",
            "B. will ",
            "C. will bought ",
            "D. will have bought"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Susi _______________ (still live) in Paris in September.", 
        answer:   "A. will still be living  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. will still be living  ",
            "B. will still live ",
            "C. will still have lived ",
            "D. is still living"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Do you know if your parents _______________ dinner with us tomorrow?",
        answer:  "C. will be having  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. have  ",
            "B. must have ",
            "C. will be having  ",
            "D. will have had"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "There is ___ new maths teacher at the school this year.",
        answer:   "A. a ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. a ",
            "B. *",
            "C. the  ",
            "D. an"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Mumbai is one of the most __________ populated cities in the world.",
        answer: "D. densely",
        optionqa: [
            "A.  dense  ",
            "B. densed ",
            "C. densening ",
            "D. densely"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The train company ___________ passengers who travel without a ticket.",
        answer:  "B. fines  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. charges ",
            "B. fines  ",
            "C. punishes ",
            "D. helps"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "There is still a place for Dr Phillips at the conference, ___ he wants to come.",
        answer: "B. assuming",
        optionqa: [
            "A. as soon as ",
            "B. assuming",
            "C. unless",
            "D. thinking"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "It’s ___________ that your holiday request will be approved. This is our busiest period!",
        answer:  "B. unlikely  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. Definitely",
            "B. unlikely  ",
            "C. possible",
            "D. doubt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "When people are angry about the conditions they live in, it can often lead to ________________.",
        answer:  "C. social unrest  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. poverty  ",
            "B. homelessness  ",
            "C. social unrest  ",
            "D. inequality"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "If they ____________ Titanic, ____________ you watch it?",
        answer: "C. remade/would ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. remade/will  ",
            "B. remake/would ",
            "C. remade/would ",
            "D. had remade/would"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "If I ___________ to 10 children when I was young, I wouldn’t ____________ as much free time as I do.", 
        answer: "A. had given a birth/have ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. had given a birth/have ",
            "B. gave a birth/have had  ",
            "C. had given a birth/have had  ",
            "D. gave a birth/have"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " I’d __________ more than I do now if I __________ better grades at school.",
        answer: "C. earn/get  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. have earned/got ",
            "B. earn/get ",
            "C. earn/get  ",
            "D. earned/got"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "___________ being very popular, the museum had to close. ",
        answer:  "C. Despite ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. Although ",
            "B. Even though",
            "C. Despite ",
            "D. However"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "___________ she loved modern art, she couldn’t say she understood it.",
        answer: "B. Although ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. However  ",
            "B. Although ",
            "C. In spite of ",
            "D. Despite"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "He bought her a gold necklace as a present. ____________, she didn’t like it when she saw it.",
        answer: "B. However",
        optionqa: [
            "A. Even though",
            "B. However",
            "C. In spite of",
            "D. Despite"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "The bank robber was ____________ as an elderly man.",
        answer: "B. disguised  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. tracked  ",
            "B. disguised  ",
            "C. demonstrated  ",
            "D. arrested"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "It’s getting dark! We should ____________ the town.",
        answer: "C. head for",
        optionqa: [
            "A. pursue ",
            "B. chase ",
            "C. head for",
            "D. go"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Some of the trees have fallen down. There ___ have been a storm last night.",
        answer: "C. must ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. may not",
            "B. couldn’t ",
            "C. must ",
            "D. should "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "James isn’t at work this week. He ___ have been working too hard. Or maybe he’s on holiday.",
        answer: "B. might",
        optionqa: [
            "A. couldn’t",
            "B. might",
            "C. must",
            "D. should "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Before moving house, we thought _____________ a lot.",
        answer: "D. it through",
        optionqa: [
            "A. through it",
            "B. throught through ",
            "C. thought through",
            "D. it through"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "It _______ that the robber was a bird. That morning, she had seen a bird fly into her room and pick up some jewellery.",
        answer: "A. turned out ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. turned out ",
            "B. was assumed ",
            "C. was an evidence  ",
            "D. was a hoax"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "We remember ____________ this place a lot as children.",
        answer: "A. visiting",
        optionqa: [
            "A. visiting",
            "B. to visit  ",
            "C. visit   ",
            "D. used to visit"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "I've had enough of this job. I can’t wait __________ on holiday.",
        answer: "B. to go  ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. going ",
            "B. to go  ",
            "C. go ",
            "D. to going"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "If you want to buy a car, it would be worth __________ (look) in the local paper.",
        answer: "D. looking",
        optionqa: [
            "A. looked ",
            "B. to look  ",
            "C. look  ",
            "D. looking"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "‘I can sleep all day.’   He _____________________.",
        answer: "B. told me he could sleep all day ",
        optionqa: [
            "A. told me I could have slept all day ",
            "B. told me he could sleep all day ",
            "C. told me I could sleep all day  ",
            "D. told me he could have slept all day"
        ]
    }
];



